Believe Me: The Abduction of Lisa McVey is a drama, tv
movie, crime film directed by Jim Donovan.
On the night she plans on taking her own life, 17-year-old 'Lisa McVey' is
kidnapped and finds herself fighting to stay alive and is raped.
She manages to talk her attacker into releasing her, but when she returns home, no one believes her
story except for one detective, who suspects she was abducted by a serial killer.
Based on horrifying true events.
Lisa McVey, played by Katie Douglas.
Sgt. Larry Pinkerton, played by David James Elliott.
Bobby Joe Long, played by Rossif Sutherland.
Lorrie, played by Amanda Arcuri.
Det. Wolf, played by Chris Owens.
Morris, played by Bruno Verdoni.
Believe Me: The Abduction of Lisa McVey is a 2018 American true
crime film, filmed in Canada, directed by Jim Donovan.
The film was released on September 30, 2018, by Lifetime in
United States  and by Showcase in Canada.
On June 4, 2021, it was released worldwide by Netflix.
The film stars Katie Douglas, Rossif Sutherland, and David James Elliott.
The film recounts the true story of Lisa McVey who was abducted and
raped for 26 hours by serial killer Bobby Joe Long in 1984.
In addition to its television broadcast, the film also received a special theatrical screening
in Tampa, at the very same theater where Bobby Joe Long was arrested in 1984.
The screening of this movie was attended by the real Lisa McVey Noland.
The film explores themes of suicide, sexual abuse,
kidnapping, detective, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.